Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.10 (1963: May 17)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.11 (1963: May 31)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.12 (1963: June 14)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.13 (1963: June 28)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.14 (1963: July 12)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.15 (1963: July 26)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.16 (1963: Aug. 9)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.17 (1963: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.18 (1963: Sept. 6)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.19 (1963: Sept. 20)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.20 (1963: Oct. 4)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.21 (1963: Oct. 18)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.22 (1963: Nov. 1)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.23 (1963: Nov. 15)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.24 (1963: Nov. 29)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.25 (1963: Dec. 13)
  - Item 26: West Coast Sailors, 1963; Publication (Box 142, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.26:no.26 (1963: Dec. 27)
- West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1964: Jan. 10)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.2 (1964: Jan. 24)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.3 (1964: Feb. 7)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.4 (1964: Feb. 21)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.5 (1964: Mar. 6)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.6 (1964: Mar. 20)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.7 (1964: Apr. 10)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.8 (1964: Apr. 24)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.9 (1964: May 8)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.10 (1964: May 22)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.11 (1964: June 5)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.12 (1964: June 19)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.15 (1964: Aug. 7)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.16 (1964: Aug. 21)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.17 (1964: Sept. 11)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.18 (1964: Sept. 25)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.19 (1964: Oct. 9)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.20 (1964: Oct. 23)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.21 (1964: Nov. 6)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.22 (1964: Nov. 20)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1964; Publication (Box 143, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.23 (1964: Dec. 11)
- West Coast Sailors, 1965-1966 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.1 (1965: Jan. 8)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.2 (1965: Jan. 22)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.3 (1965: Feb. 5)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.4 (1965: Feb. 19)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.5 (1965: Mar. 5)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.6 (1965: Mar. 19)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.7 (1965: Apr. 9)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.8 (1965: Apr. 23)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.9 (1965: May 7)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.10 (1965: May 21)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.11 (1965: June 11)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.12 (1965: June 25)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.13 (1965: July 9)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.14 (1965: July 23)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.16 (1965: Aug. 20)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.17 (1965: Sept. 10)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.18 (1965: Sept. 24)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.19 (1965: Oct. 8)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.20 (1965: Oct. 22)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.21 (1965: Nov. 5)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.22 (1965: Nov. 19)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.23 (1965: Dec. 10)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1965; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.24 (1965: Dec. 24)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.23 (1966: Dec. 9)
- West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1966: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.3 (1966: Feb. 11)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.4 (1966: Feb. 25)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1966: Mar. 11)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1966: Mar. 25)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1966: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.8 (1966: Apr. 22)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.9 (1966: May 6)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.10 (1966: May 20)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.11 (1966: June 10)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.12 (1966: June 24)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.13 (1966: July 8)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.14 (1966: July 22)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.15 (1966: Aug. 5)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.16 (1966: Aug. 19)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.17 (1966: Sept. 9)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.18 (1966: Sept. 23)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.19 (1966: Oct. 7)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.20 (1966: Oct. 21)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.21 (1966: Nov. 11)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.22 (1966: Nov. 25)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1966; Publication (Box 143, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.24 (1966: Dec. 23)
- West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.1 (1967: Jan. 6)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.2 (1967: Jan. 20)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.3 (1967: Feb. 10)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.4 (1967: Feb. 24)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.5 (1967: Mar. 10)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.6 (1967: Mar. 24)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.7 (1967: Apr. 7)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.8 (1967: Apr. 21)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.9 (1967: May 5)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.10 (1967: May 19)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.11 (1967: June 9)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.12 (1967: June 23)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.13 (1967: July 7)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.14 (1967: July 21)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.15 (1967: Aug. 11)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.16 (1967: Aug. 25)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.17 (1967: Sept. 8)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.18 (1967: Sept. 22)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.19 (1967: Oct. 6)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.20 (1967: Oct. 20)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.21 (1967: Nov. 10)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.22 (1967: Nov. 24)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.23 (1967: Dec. 8)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1967; Publication (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.24 (1967: Dec. 22)
- West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1968: Jan. 5)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1968: Feb. 9)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1968: Feb. 23)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1968: Mar. 8)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1968: Mar. 22)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1968: Apr. 5)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.8 (1968: Apr. 19)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.9 (1968: May 10)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1968: May 24)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.11 (1968: June 7)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.12 (1968: June 21)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.13 (1968: July 5)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.14 (1968: July 19)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.16 (1968: Aug. 23)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.17 (1968: Sept. 6)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.18 (1968: Sept. 20)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.19 (1968: Oct. 11)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.20 (1968: Oct. 25)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.21 (1968: Nov. 8)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.22 (1968: Nov. 22)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.23 (1968: Dec. 6)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1968; Publication (Box 143, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.24 (1968: Dec. 20)
- West Coast Sailors, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1969: Jan. 10)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.2 (1969: Jan. 24)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.3 (1969: Feb. 7)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1969: Feb. 21)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1969: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1969: Mar. 21)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1969: Apr. 11)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.8 (1969: Apr. 25)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.9 (1969: May 9)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.10 (1969: May 23)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.11 (1969: June 6)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1969: June 20)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.13 (1969: July 11)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.14 (1969: July 25)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.15 (1969: Aug. 8)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.16 (1969: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.17 (1969: Sept. 5)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.18 (1969: Sept. 19)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.19 (1969: Oct 10)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.20 (1969: Oct. 24)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.21 (1969: Nov. 7)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.22 (1969: Nov. 21)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.23 (1969: Dec. 5)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1969; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.24 (1969: Dec. 19)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1970: Jan. 9)
  - Item 26: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1970: Jan. 23)
  - Item 27: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1970: Feb. 6)
  - Item 28: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1970: Feb. 20)
  - Item 29: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.5 (1970: Mar. 6)
  - Item 30: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.7 (1970: Apr. 10)
  - Item 31: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.9 (1970: May 8)
  - Item 32: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1970: May 22)
  - Item 33: West Coast Sailors, 1970; Publication (Box 143, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1970: June 19)